Finding Aid for Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated.
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Signs, Seals, and Symbols,undated (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Softball,undated (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Soccer, Women’s,undated (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Speakers,undated (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Special Education Department,undated (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Special Olympics,undated (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Speech Department,undated (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Sports Medicine,undated (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - Colored Slides, M-S: Sports Program Ads,undated (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Student Activities,undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Student Activities Center,undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: No Label,undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Teacher Education,undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Testing Center,undated (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Telecommunications,undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Theatre and Dramatic Arts,undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Track, Men’s and Women’s,undated (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: University Center,undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: Volleyball,undated (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Colored Slides, S-W: wrestling,undated (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Negatives, 1950s-60s, CDs,2012 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #761-1029,2000 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #1030-169,2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #170-420,2001 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #421-699,2001 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #700-949, 2001,2001 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #950-end, 2001, 1-89, 20022001-2002 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #90-379,2002 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #380-639,2002 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, #640-end, #1-102,2002-2005 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Note Card Box: Name Cards, A-C,undated (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Note Card Box: Name Cards, D-Ha,undated (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Note Card Box: Name Cards, He-Mc,undated (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Note Card Box: Name Cards, M-R, W (end of Ws)-Z,undated (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Note Card Box: Name Cards, S-W (first part of Ws),undated (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Historical Photographs, Index Cards, Negatives,1973, 1965-1967 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1946-1962, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1946-1962 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1957-1958 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1957-1962 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1958-1959, 1960s (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1953-1957 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1952-1957 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1951-1954 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #187-488,1968 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #1-349,1969 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Negatives Strips #350-250,1969-1970 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #1-50, 1970, #251-605, 1971,1970-1971 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #51-399,1971 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #400-479 1972, #1-299, 1971,1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #300-514 1973, #1-200, 1972,1972-1973 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #201-599,1973 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #600-635, 1973, 1-329, 1974,1973-1974 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #330-656,1974 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Negatives Strips #1-450,1975 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Negatives Strips #451-704, 1975, #1-175, 1976,1975-1976 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Negatives Strips #176-483, 1976, #1-69, 1977,1976-1977 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #70-479,1977 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #480-715, 1977, #1-199, 1978,1977-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #200, 1978, 1-200, 1979,1978-1979 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #201-380, 1980, 1-209, 1973,1980, 1973 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #210-539,1973 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #540-576, 1980, #1-299, 1981,1980-1981 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #300-441, 1981, #1-199, 1982,1981-1982 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #200-450, 1982, #1-115, 1983,1982-1983 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #116-443,1983 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #1-339,1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #340-505, 1984, #1-170, 1985,1984-1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #171-529, 1985,1985 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #530-653, 1985, #1-239, 1986,1985-1986 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #240-579, 1986,1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #580-653, 1986, #1-279, 1987,1986-1987 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #280-645,1987 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #646-672, 1987, #1-310, 1988,1987-1988 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #311-629,1988 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #630-684, 1988, #1-282, 1989,1988-1989 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #283-658, 1989,1989 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #659-728, 1989, #1-325, 1990,1989-1990 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #326-666, 1990,1990 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #667-727, 1990, #1-323, 1991,1990-1991 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #324-502, 1991, #1-191, 1992,1991-1992 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #192-532, 1992, #1-21, 1993,1992-1993 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #22-379,1993 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #380-540, 1993, #1-202, 1994,1993-1994 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #203-549, 1994,1994 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #550-578, 1994, #1-329, 1995,1994-1995 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Negatives # 330-568, 1995, #1-95, 1996,1995-1996 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #96-429,1996 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #430-620, 1996, #1-139, 1997,1996-1997 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #140-444,1997 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #445-710, 1997, #1-96, 1998,1997-1998 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #97-455,1998 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #456-788,1998 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #789-834, 1998, #1-279, 1999,1998-1999 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #280-589, 1999,1999 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #590-853, 1999, #1-25, CDs, 2000,1999-2000 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #26-327,2000 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #328-616,2000 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Negatives #617-760,2000 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Negatives,1940s-1960s (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - (Slide Box 1): Alumni Field,undated (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - (Slide Box 1): Baseball B – C,undated (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - (Slide Box 1): Baseball F – K,undated (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - (Slide Box 1): Baseball M – W,undated (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - (Slide Box 1): Basketball,undated (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - (Slide Box 1): ’75 Baseball Action ,1975 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - (Slide Box 1): ’76 Baseball Action (small slide box 1),1976 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - (Slide Box 1): ’76 Baseball Action (small slide box 2),1976 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - (Slide Box 1): California Bowl,undated (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - (Slide Box 1): Cheerleaders,undated (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - (Slide Box 1): Coaches and Other Personnel,undated (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - (Slide Box 1): Finch,undated (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - (Slide Box 1): Field Hockey,undated (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - (Slide Box 1): Football,undated (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - (Slide Box 1): Football Action,undated (Box 189, Folder 15)
  - (Slide Box 1): Football Players,undated (Box 189, Folder 16)
  - (Slide Box 1): Gymnastics,undated (Box 189, Folder 17)
  - (Slide Box 1): Fred Jacoby Mid-American Conference,undated (Box 189, Folder 18)
  - (Slide Box 1): Dave Keilitz Baseball,undated (Box 189, Folder 19)
  - (Slide Box 1): Ted Kjolhede,undated (Box 1989, Folder 20)
  - (Slide Box 2): Ken Kopke, Trainer,undated (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - (Slide Box 2): Roy Kramer,undated (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - (Slide Box 2): Dean Kreiner,undated (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - (Slide Box 2): Logo Indian Head,undated (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - (Slide Box 2): Marching Band,undated (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - (Slide Box 2): Tony Miele,undated (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - (Slide Box 2): Jerry Misner, Swimming,undated (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - (Slide Box 2): Dick Parfitt, Basketball,undated (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - (Slide Box 2): Perry Shorts Stadium (small slide box 1),undated (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - (Slide Box 2): Perry Shorts Stadium (small slide box 2),undated (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - (Slide Box 2): Dan Rose, Athletic Director,undated (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - (Slide Box 2): Rose Center,undated (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - (Slide Box 2): Don Sazima, Track,undated (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - (Slide Box 2): Walt Schneider, Basketball,undated (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - (Slide Box 2): Chick Sherwood, Wrestling,undated (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - (Slide Box 2): Track,undated (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - (Slide Box 2): Wrestling,undated (Box 190, Folder 17)
  - (Slide Box 2): Wrestling Room and Gym Room,undated (Box 190, Folder 18)
  - (Slide Box 2): Dean William Theunissen,undated (Box 190, Folder 19)
  - (Slide Box 2): Leo Wisneski, Golf,undated (Box 190, Folder 20)
  - (.5 cu. ft. box) Digital Image Database List (for 444 KB),2002-2012 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - (.5 cu. ft. box) Digital Image Database List (for 758 KB) (Folder 1 of 3),1997-2001 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - (.5 cu. ft. box) Digital Image Database List (for 758 KB) (Folder 2 of 3),1997-2001 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - (.5 cu. ft. box) Digital Image Database List (for 758 KB) (Folder 3 of 3),1997-2001 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 179 Lem Tucker Tribute from BCA,1998 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 786 Lem Tucker Dub from FACIT,1998 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 784 Lem Tucker Dub from FACIT pt. 1-2,1999 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 781 Lem Tucker Dub from FACIT,2000 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 782 Lem Tucker Dub from FACIT pt. 1-2,2000 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 783 Lem Tucker Dub from FACIT pt. 1,2000 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 740 [A--- (spelling?) faded] Festival,2003 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 833 Jerry Tubbs Warriner History,2006 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 692 Nichol Trio,2007 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 718 College Life and the Law Estab. Shot,2007 (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 719 College Life and the Law Handheld,2007 (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 720 College Life and the Law Stage Left,2007 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 721 SAE Baja Championship Tape #2,2007 (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 722 SAE Baja Championship Tape #1,2007 (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 691 Herb Deromedi Interview,2000 (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 693 Leadership E. Bushley,2000 (Box 192, Folder 16)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 694 Body Scanner AIP,2000 (Box 192, Folder 17)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 695 Pottery Demo HGDL,2000 (Box 192, Folder 18)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 969 Driving Simulator AIP,2003 (Box 192, Folder 19)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 697 Campus Climate Cam 1 pt.1,2006 (Box 192, Folder 20)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 698 R. Flesher Big Think,2007 (Box 192, Folder 21)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 699 Art Installation R. Flesher,2007 (Box 192, Folder 22)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 700 Pat Benson, Sarah Adams Bookmark,2007 (Box 192, Folder 23)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 701 Diversity Sculpt N. Art Studio,undated (Box 192, Folder 24)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 703 Extra Enberg, O’Kelly’s,2007 (Box 192, Folder 25)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 704 Deer Center Dedication,2007 (Box 192, Folder 26)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 705 Dick Enberg at O’Kelly’s,2007 (Box 192, Folder 27)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 706 MS [Master]-Enberg Dedication,2007 (Box 192, Folder 28)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 707 Nedra Frodge MSF,2007 (Box 192, Folder 29)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 708 K. Corbett, N. Frodge MSF,2007 (Box 192, Folder 30)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 790 Math, Sci, Tech Camps,2007 (Box 192, Folder 31)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 737 Mike Owens Donor Appreciation,2007 (Box 192, Folder 32)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 741 Hartzler, Nichol Trio,2007 (Box 192, Folder 33)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 742 M. Shiley MSF,2007 (Box 192, Folder 34)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 743 Nichol Trio with Reid MSF at Dallas,12007 (Box 192, Folder 35)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 753 Kulhavi Kottamau Event Med Center,2007 (Box 192, Folder 36)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 757 Special Olympics Open FieldCam pt. 1,2007 (Box 192, Folder 37)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 757 Special Olympics Open FieldCam pt. 2,2007 (Box 192, Folder 38)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 758 Special Olympics Open FieldCam pt. 3,2007 (Box 192, Folder 39)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 759 Special Olympics Open Handheld pt. 1,2007 (Box 192, Folder 40)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 760 Special Olympics Open Handheld pt. 2,2007 (Box 192, Folder 41)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 761 Special Olympics Open UpCam pt. 1,2007 (Box 192, Folder 42)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 762 Special Olympics Open Upcam pt. 2,2007 (Box 192, Folder 43)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 763 Special Olympics Open Events pt. 2,2007 (Box 192, Folder 44)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 764 Lois Arnold,2007 (Box 192, Folder 45)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette no# David Gillingham Nat. Sound,2007 (Box 192, Folder 46)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 709 Campus Climate Cam 1 pt. 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 47)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 710 Campus Climate Cam 2 pt. 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 48)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 711 Campus Climate Cam 2 pt. 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 49)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 712 Sarah Adams, P. Benson Cam 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 50)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 713 Sarah Adams, P. Benson Cam 3,2008 (Box 192, Folder 51)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 714 Sarah Adams, P. Benson Cam 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 52)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 715 Glenn Ware CBA,2008 (Box 192, Folder 53)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 723 Mike Fields,2008 (Box 192, Folder 54)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 724 Myth Busters pt. 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 55)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 725 Myth Busters pt. 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 56)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 726 Student Environmental Alliance,2008 (Box 192, Folder 57)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 727 SEA Deb Rowe, pt. 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 58)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 728 SEA Deb Rowe, pt.2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 59)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 729 Plachta Tribute pt. 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 60)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 730 Plachta Tribute pt. 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 61)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 731 Plachta Tribute pt. 3,2008 (Box 192, Folder 62)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 732 Plachta Tribute pt. 4,2008 (Box 192, Folder 63)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 733 Bryan Wiefrich, Donor,2008 (Box 192, Folder 64)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 734 Polar Plunge HVX,2008 (Box 192, Folder 65)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 735 Polar Plunge DVX,2008 (Box 192, Folder 66)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 736 Tim Otteman RPL Fundraisers,2008 (Box 192, Folder 67)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 739 (1st cassette) Learn to Swim and 3 VS 3 B-ball,2008 (Box 192, Folder 68)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 739 (2nd cassette) Donor Appreciation,2008 (Box 192, Folder 69)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 744 Flec Car,2008 (Box 192, Folder 70)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 745 Eliz. Carpenter Donor,2008 (Box 192, Folder 71)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 752 Earth Day,2008 (Box 192, Folder 72)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 1: video microcassette 773 IC Stand-ups,2008 (Box 192, Folder 73)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 746 Events Center,2008 (Box 192, Folder 74)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 747 Dave Heeke, Events Center,2008 (Box 192, Folder 75)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 748 Sue Guevara, Events Center,2008 (Box 192, Folder 76)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 749 M Rao, Med Center,2008 (Box 192, Folder 77)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 750 B Ebner Event Center,2008 (Box 192, Folder 78)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 751 School Luncheon Alumni / Development,2008 (Box 192, Folder 79)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 765 Herb Deromedi,2008 (Box 192, Folder 80)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 766 Gear Up B-Roll,2008 (Box 192, Folder 81)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 767 Gear Up Interviews,2008 (Box 192, Folder 82)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 768 Make a Wish (MAW) Cyclists,2008 (Box 192, Folder 83)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 756 Make a Wish (MAW) Cyclists Interview pt. 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 84)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 769 Make a Wish (MAW) Cyclists Interview pt. 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 85)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 770 Mary Henley Gear Up,2008 (Box 192, Folder 86)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 771 Botanical Gardens Groundbreaking,2008 (Box 192, Folder 87)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 772 Caponigro Media Lab,2008 (Box 192, Folder 88)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 773 Caponigro Media Lab,2008 (Box 192, Folder 89)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 774 Special O (Olympics) Events pt. 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 90)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 776 Scott Harding Interview,2008 (Box 192, Folder 91)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 777 Steve Berglund Interview,2008 (Box 192, Folder 92)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 778 Inside Central Stand Ups,2008 (Box 192, Folder 93)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 780 Lem Tucker,2008 (Box 192, Folder 94)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 784 Pig Out in Park,2008 (Box 192, Folder 95)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 787 Events Center Kickoff,2008 (Box 192, Folder 96)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 788 Frosty Willey Caldw,2008 (Box 192, Folder 97)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 789 Rec Book Art Hardin,2008 (Box 192, Folder 98)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 790 R Heuberger,2008 (Box 192, Folder 99)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 791 Steve Berglund Rehearsal,2008 (Box 192, Folder 100)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 792 Al Wiley,2008 (Box 192, Folder 101)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 793 Gold Dragon,2008 (Box 192, Folder 102)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 794 Steve Berglund Digressions,2008 (Box 192, Folder 103)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 795 Frost Wyrick,2008 (Box 192, Folder 104)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 796 Football PSAs, 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 105)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 797 Football PSAs [1],2008 (Box 192, Folder 106)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 798 Wellness Fair,2008 (Box 192, Folder 107)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 799 Dog Food,2008 (Box 192, Folder 108)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 800 Kevin Locke pt. 1,2008 (Box 192, Folder 109)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 801 Kevin Locke pt. 2,2008 (Box 192, Folder 110)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 802 Tammy Griffi,2008 (Box 192, Folder 111)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 803 Nimkee Wellness [Center],2008 (Box 192, Folder 112)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 804 Wellness B-roll,2008 (Box 192, Folder 113)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 805 Rock Wall,2008 (Box 192, Folder 114)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 806 R. Schumaker,2008 (Box 192, Folder 115)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 807 Lindsay Stand-up,2008 (Box 192, Folder 116)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 808 Special Olympics Knitting,2008 (Box 192, Folder 117)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 809 Special Olympics Scarves,2009 (Box 192, Folder 118)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 810 URec SD B-roll,2009 (Box 192, Folder 119)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 811 Chad Stirret,2009 (Box 192, Folder 120)
  - Microcassettes in 3 box lids: Box Lid 2: video microcassette 812 John Kujat,2009 (Box 192, Folder 121)